His passion is business by day, murder by night.
The Banker is a crime, thriller, horror film directed by William Webb.
High-priced prostitutes are being systematically murdered, their corpses mutilated, and
a bizarre South American symbol painted in blood is found at the scene.
The cop investigating is out to solve the crime before his ex
wife, a reporter, becomes the next victim.
Dan, played by Robert Forster.
Sharon, played by Shanna Reed.
Spaulding Osbourne, played by Duncan Regehr.
Cowboy, played by Jeff Conaway.
Fowler, played by Leif Garrett.
Lloyd, played by Richard Roundtree.
A banker provides financial banking services and typically works in a bank.
The word may also refer to:
Banker (ancient), a person providing financial services in ancient Greece and Rome
Banker (surname), a surname
Bank engine or helper engine, a locomotive that helps other engines up steep hills
Bankers (train), American passenger train
The Banker, an international financial affairs publication
The Banker (Deal or No Deal UK), the antagonist on the British game show Deal or No Deal
"The Banker" (The Office), an episode of the sixth season of the American television show
The Office
The Bankers, 1975 book by Martin Mayer
The Banker (1989 film), an American horror-mystery film starring Robert Forster, Shanna Reed, and Duncan Regehr
The Banker (2015 film), a Nigerian drama film
The Banker (2020 film), an American drama film starring Anthony Mackie
Banker (horse), an Australian racehorse, winner of the 1863 Melbourne Cup
Banker (card player), the player who controls the play in a gambling game
The Banker (TV series), a 2019 South Korean television series
The film explores themes of banker, prostitute, wife, investigation, victim.
The tone is dark and intense.